// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "y + 30 = 70",
    answer: "40",
    options: [
      "40",
      "100",
      "30",
      "70"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "50 - (4 x 10)",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "20",
      "50",
      "40",
      "10"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "70 x 0.5",
    answer: "35",
    options: [
      "3",
      "35",
      "350",
      "45"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the value of the 4 in the number 549 632",
    answer: "40,000",
    options: [
      "hundred thousands",
      "ten thousands",
      "40,000",
      "400,000"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " y - 60 = 10",
    answer: "70",
    options: [
      "40",
      "50",
      "70",
      "80"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Even numbers are multiples of 2 E.g. 0,2,4,6..",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "Can't Say",
      "Not Defined"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A class of students count the number of sea stars they find on a field trip to the beach. They then make a pictograph that shows how many sea stars each student found. The key to the pictograph is shown that is 1 star picture= 5 sea stars. If the pictograph has 20 sea stars, how many total sea stars were found by the students? ⭐=5",
    answer: "100",
    options: [
      "50",
      "75",
      "100",
      "150"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "¹²∕₂₀ Simplify this fraction",
    answer: "³∕₅",
    options: [
      "²∕₁₀",
      "⁴∕₅",
      "³∕₅",
      "⁶∕₁₁"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The space programme has 4 astronauts in outer space and 14 astronauts on Earth. What is the ratio of the number of astronauts in outer space to the number of astronauts on Earth?",
    answer: "4:14",
    options: [
      "14:4",
      "28:4",
      "4:14",
      "18:8"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "?",
    answer: "?",
    options: [
      "?",
      "?",
      "?",
      "?"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
